Oh, misty eye of the mountain below
Keep careful watch of my brother's souls
And should the sky be filled with fire and smoke
Keep watching over your insides
If this is to end in fire
Then we shall all burn together
Watch the flames climb high into the night
Calling out Father O
Stand by and we will watch the flames burn
Oven on the mountainside
And if we should die tonight
Then we should all die together
Raise a glass of wine
For the last time
Calling out Father O
Prepare as we will
Watch the flames burn
Oven on the mountainside
Desolation comes upon the sky
Now I see fire
Inside the mountain I see fire
Burning the trees and I see fire
Hollow in soul I see fire
Blood in the breeze
And I hope that you remember me
Oh, should my people fold in
Surely I'll do the same
Come find in mountain holes
We got too close to the flame
Calling out Father O
Hold fast and we will
Watch the flames burn
Oven on the mountainside
Desolation comes upon the sky
Now I see fire
Inside the mountain I see fire
Burning the trees and I see fire
Hollow in soul I see fire
Blood in the breeze
And I hope that you remember me
And if the night is burning
I will cover my eyes
For if the dark wind turns
Then my brothers will die
And as the sky is falling down
It crushed into this lonely town
And with that shadow upon the ground
I hear my people screaming now
Now I see fire
Inside the mountain I see fire
Burning the trees and I see fire
Hollow in soul I see fire
Blood in the breeze I see fire
Oh, you know it's on a city burn
And I see fire
Feel the heat upon my skin
And I see fire burn
Oven on the mountainside