Run it down, then sign it up So run it down, get your money up
I put money down on all of us On my people now, on what I love
Ooh, baby, it's dangerous Your problems are just not the same to us
We're dealing with things you ain't seen before We're feeling the weight of our instances
We're hailing our ways that don't last a long Don't happen the time in the diabetes
No help for the weak, but the lick is strong Plenty here, boy, for all of us
Now bring out the drums and the bitch On my homies got restoration that I said wouldn't work
Bring out the guns and the bitch Here to load up a clip, I'm gon' show up in a place with a car
I see the bums, I be wishing we ending the ditch Here to playin' and see I'm at heart
I see the love that we giving, the love that we getting Sure everything comin' for zero
We're from nothin' to something Got all of a job and that shit that we made from the air
We're in front runnin' and gunnin' With nothin' to stop it, they're beatin' the neighborhood bruh
They ain't a person alive, they be matchin' the vibe And they honestly ain't even bad
They're in the door with the drive And the vision like I haven't lost sight
Go look in the mirror, babe So run it up, the sun is up
To run it down, get your money up I put money down, on all of us
On my people now, on what I love Ooh, baby, we run it up
Yeah, they demand that the sun is up There's no rest, do we run it down
We're different, we got your money up But leave it like I put money down
I'm bettin' the odds on all of us I do it for all of my people now
Put that up, everything that I love Yeah, on everything that I love
Yeah, ain't nothin' that come up up
Now we go from angry and mad to happy and glad To find a solution for us
We go from sorry inside to ready to grab our weapons And get to the punch
I want the money, the cash, the mule, the bag, the currency, stacking it up
We want the freedom, the labor, the freedom to have The things we'll be lackin' my brush
So what are we lackin'? I could point it down, so much that's around
Bet I'll settle down, no point doin' that All they send the hounds, bite me in the eyes
Put me in the ground, tell me in the eyes, come to carry down
From those who came up before me I made a change out the story
Find me at work and I'm on it Find me with people I'm on it, man
Your death is around every corner When life isn't free for a person, dark
You act like an animal corner Savage is speaking a language, oh
You don't understand your corner So nobody need an advantage
Now we need a balance and order But you know there's never that case
Never a chance that they're changing their ways There's never a choice that they're giving to you
No, we'll never be just as a phase We sing for the sorrow and dance for the pain
You're one to follow, it's just you and me I swear that it's coming, we startin' the day
But we'll wake up tomorrow and things are the same, die
I mean it, what did I tell you the fuck you do?