Maybe I was wrong and you were right
But I don't really wanna have this fight
I just wanna feel like I belong
And every time my heart sings back to you
You are my morning and my truth
I know that I can do is sing this song
It ain't that long
And nothing says I love you like your eyes
From my lips with carbon dioxide
I just wanna feel like I deserve you
Cause you deserve me
Maybe it's the way that you can see
What I'm missing, what I can never be
I just wanna feel like I deserve you
Cause you deserve me
Maybe you were wrong and I was right
But I don't care, won't you stay another night?
I just need some time to be myself
I couldn't say I need you on that night
When you left and I lost all track of time
I just want you close so I can feel you
Can you feel me?
And nothing says I love you like the words that were never said
If only there was peace around us baby
You would hear me
And maybe it's the way that lovers do
I just want for me, what I want for you
Only with the sun above us maybe
You would see me
And even if you leave I may be fine
Cause my heart, it has its own design
And even if you never see it baby
You're all that I need
Maybe it's the silence in your eyes
Maybe it's the light like when you're shy
Maybe it's the mystery of your love
All I need is a sign from the stars above
Maybe it's the way that you breathe
Maybe it's the man that you see in me
Maybe it's the fragrance of your hair
I just want to kiss you when you're there
I just want you all around me baby
Can we make that happen please?